I want to break up.
She found out about the real me.
I'm in love with you, Ama.
I'm sorry.
Is this true?
[Love Triangle]
I'm so sorry.
[Chiaki Hosho's Hidden Past]
What is this?
You're working hard.
I know that.
I don't want your future ruined
by an article like that.
Even now, I'll continue to support you.
I still love you.
I want to stay by your side.
I still love you, Chiaki.
Women easily mix up love and guilt.
I love you, Ama.
It's Seira's first Japanese drama in a while.
You're Ama Minase, right?
You're Chiaki's girlfriend now, aren't you?
That was jealousy.
It must be hard for you.
He's so possessive.
Stop it.
You're adorable.
Oh, really.
You really are twisted.
That's funny, coming from you.
I want you...
to be happy.
How's the new filming set?
The staff are all nice
and serious about their work.
What's wrong?
I still can't connect with the character.
I see.
In a fit of jealous rage,
she kills the person she was cheating with.
But I can't grasp those emotions.
I can't only rely
on my own experiences forever, huh?
Hey, Ama.
How are your co-stars?
I wonder if I know any of them.
You see, Chiaki...
What?
Never mind.
Everyone's really kind.
So easy to read.
You're so cute.
What?
It's nothing.
I just wish I could
be of some help to you, Ama.
Good luck with your shoot.
You really are twisted.
I know that better than anyone.
I wish I had a cage to lock Ama away in.
She belongs only to me.
I don't want anyone to see her.
No one can touch her.
You're...
You said you love me the most.
Was that a lie?
That's...
Don't look at any other woman.
Look only at me!
- Cut!
- That's enough...
Ms. Minase, that take was incredible!
I honestly thought I was going to be killed.
Ms. Minase?
Thank you very much.
Oh?
I really got into character
during today's shoot!
[I'm glad to hear it.]
[Mom]
Hello?
Hey, what's with that article?
[Growing Up With a Toxic Parent]
[Revenge Against His Mother?]
What about it?
This makes me look like some terrible mother!
That article made another man leave me,
so take responsibility!
Responsibility?
It's all true anyway.
I'm getting proper compensation for this.
I lost my job too, you know.
I can't give you money anymore.
Oh, really?
You think you can say that?
That girl who stood up for you the other day.
Ama Minase, was it?
She's pretty popular lately, isn't she?
I could sell a scandal about that girl
for a pretty penny.
Stop!
Don't drag Ama into this!
Fine, I get it.
I'll get the money ready.
No matter how much you hate me,
I'm never letting you go.
Forever.
Until the day I die.
But I'll never let you go
until the day I die.
Alright, hurry up then.
Good work today.
You and Chiaki...
are pretty similar.
Huh?
Good work today.
What time are you done?
I'll come pick you up.
Thanks for coming...
Did you see anyone weird?
- Huh?
- Like someone following you?
No, I'm fine.
I see.
What's wrong?
No,
it's nothing.
What's that attitude towards your mother?
Hand them over, now.
Your bank book and card.
Are you listening?
You got paid, didn't you?
Hurry up! Give them to me!
Don't get cocky
just because you're a celebrity.
Your face is all you've got.
That face...
You look just like your father.
You're nothing but trouble!
Women exist to hurt me.
So I'll hurt them first.
I've always thought that, but...
Ama saved me.
I love you,
Chiaki.
Ama loves me.
I never want to let her go.
Stop!
I won't let her go.
If it's to protect Ama,
I'll do whatever it takes.
But...
I'm never letting you go.
Forever.
Until the day I die.
Am I...
able to...
protect Ama?
Chiaki, is there anything I can help with?
Oh, no!
Does it hurt?
Yeah, it hurts.
I know!
The greedy little ghost
is gonna gobble up all the ouchies!
Nom, nom, nom!
I do this for my little brothers.
Sorry.
Thank you.
How can I get rid of this anxiety?
It's okay to sleep.
No, I'm okay.
Sorry, I fell asleep.
You're exhausted.
You should rest.
I have a favor to ask you, Chiaki.
What is it?
I'm planning a picnic
with my family on our next day off.
Will you come with us?
My siblings want to see you, Chiaki.
Yeah.
They'll be so happy.
Wow, amazing.
Let's eat.
Where do I start? I want this one!
Please eat up, Chiaki.
Okay.
Oh, then I want a sausage next.
A sausage?
Yeah, it's delicious.
It is delicious, isn't it?
I'm glad it's sunny!
Yeah!
Sei, Nagi, is it good?
And Chiaki's here too!
I'm so happy.
Yeah!
Here I go!
Take that!
Chiaki, you're bad at this!
So bad!
You two are pretty good.
- I did it!
- Yeah!
Alright! Sei, Nagi, get ready.
Take that!
How's that?
Your sister's awesome, right!
Awesome!
- Do it again!
- One more time!
Are you feeling well?
Yes, I've been feeling much better lately.
I'm glad to hear that.
I've put Ama through so much
because of my poor health.
She's always worked so hard for our family.
But, she looks so happy acting.
She tells me about roles
she wants to try next.
It's the first time Ama has had a dream,
so I'm overjoyed.
I see.
I heard you're the one
who gave her that dream.
Thank you so much.
Please, don't say that.
I didn't do anything.
It's because Ama has talent.
To think Ama has someone
as wonderful as you in her life...
I'm so grateful.
Huh?
It's all because of you
that my life is a mess!
I wish I'd never given birth to you.
You're nothing but trouble!
I'm... not wonderful.
Chiaki! Mom!
Sei and Nagi keep saying every day
how fun the picnic was.
I see.
I want to go again with everyone.
Yeah.
Oh... I got an offer for a late-night drama.
And I'm the lead.
That's amazing.
I still can't believe they want me.
That's great.
Yeah!
Hey, Ama.
What is it?
I think...
we should break up.
What?
Goodbye, Ama.
How are things with Chiaki?
We broke up.
It was ridiculous that
someone like me could even be with Chiaki.
I still love you, Ama.
I think you're the only one who can save him.
If Ama dates me, she'll only end up unhappy.
I'm nothing but trouble.
You saved me.
Now it's my turn to...
Chiaki! Hey, Chiaki!
I'll do anything for you, Chiaki.